衰女翻身 第一季 第三集
真好呀
Yeah! That's nice!
大家早安
Good morning, everybody.
这根葱是从哪冒出来的
Who the hell is this clown?
我是凯
I'm Kai.
他是我男友
He's my boyfriend.
你又是哪根葱
Who are you?
我是...
Well, I'm...
我是吉米
I'm Jimmy.
我滴小钢炮呀
My Goodness.
这俩真把节操当路人啊
They are really going for it, huh?
爽
Yeah!
天呐  你就不打算管管吗
Oh, my God, are you really allowing this?
你想让我怎么管
What do you want me to do about it?
管管啊  太恶心了
Something, it's disgusting.
把电视声音开大点
Just turn the TV up.
也许很快就会累趴下了
Probably tire themselves out pretty soon.
我说不清  米琪
Nah, I don't know, Mick.
现在算是你当家吧
It kind of feels like it's your department now.
你这是教我怎么当家长吗
Are you giving me parenting advice?
话说你怎么还赖在这里
Yeah, why are you even here?
没错  你在这里一无是处
Yeah, true, you contribute nothing.
你们说什么呢
Oh, what the hell are you guys talking about?
我就相当于父亲的角色
I'm the father figure.
你喜欢我画的乌龟吗
Do you like my turtle?
不  不太喜欢
no, not really.
真会摧残幼小心灵  「老爸」
Good job, Dad.
我可不会骗小孩子
Well, I'm not gonna lie to the kid.
这下完事了
Oh, there we go.
俩人消停了
Problem solved.
天啊
Oh, my God!
在不在[敲门]  我进来了
Knock, knock. Can I come in?
你可以真去敲下门
You could also actually knock.
知道了  最近好吗
Yeah. How's it going?
-一切都好吗  -很好
- Everything good? - Yep.
就玩呗
Just chillin'.
好吧
Yeah, yeah.
凯啊
So, Kai, huh?
-感觉小伙不错啊  -嗯
- He seems cool. - Yeah.
他是做哪行的  是...
What's his deal? Is he like a...
-消防员  还是模特啊  -不是
- a fireman or a model or something? - No.
不  他用回收木材做家具
No, he builds furniture out of found wood.
回收木材
Found wood.
真有这种东西啊
Found wood's a thing.
你们俩一直上床吧
So, I guess you guys are having sex, huh?
天呐  要来性教育吗
Oh, God, are we having the talk?
不  我可不想谈这事
No, I don't want to have the talk, at all.
我就是想让你知道
Listen, I just wanted to let you know that
我完全能理解
I totally get it and
你挑的男人不是盖的
you picked a good one,
高大威猛  帅气撩人
that guy is a hall of fame piece of ass.
撩得我愿意拜倒在他的胯下...
Oh, man, I'd let him do things to me...
别说了  别意淫了
Please stop! Just stop it.
好吧  重点是
All right, the point is, uh,
你是个女人  有需要  我懂
you're a woman with needs and I get it,
只要你记得用避孕套  就没事
so as long as you're using condoms, I'm cool.
我们不用
We're not.
好吧  也没什么
Oh, okay. Well, that's cool.
你的身体你做主
Your body, your choice.
我也更愿意吃避孕药
I am more of a pill person myself.
你知道避孕药的害处有多大吗
Do you have any idea how poisonous that stuff is?
避孕怎么就成毒害了  塞布丽娜
How is birth control poison, Sabrina?
药会伤害身体  造成情绪不稳定
It destroys your body and causes crazy mood swings.
宝宝也会啊
So do babies!
你怎么突然间关心...
Why do you all of a sudden care what...?
我明白了
I get it.
明白什么
Get what?
你羡慕嫉妒恨了
You're jealous.
我羡慕嫉妒恨
I'm jealous?
-没错  -嫉妒你吗
- Yeah. - What, of you?
我怎么会嫉妒你啊
Why would I be jealous of you?
因为我男人身材爆表  帅出宇宙呗
Maybe because I have a beautiful hunk of beef and you don't.
-我也有男人  -吉米吗
- I got beef. - Who, Jimmy?
丑得惊天动地的衰男吗
That packaged lunch meat?
我男人的姿色甩他几个地球半径呢
I'm over here feasting on filet mignon.
好吧  算了  不想跟你说这个了
All right, you know what? I don't want to have this conversation.
我就是不想你被人搞大肚子
I just don't want you to get pregnant,
不如你就先吃我的药吧
so why don't you just take some of my pills,
稍后你等自己去开点
until you go fill a prescription of your own.
你把避孕药放在塑料袋里吗
You keep your birth control in a plastic bag?
我在网上买的散装药
Well, I buy it in bulk online.
这样更省钱
I find it more cost effective.
我不想吃
I don't want them, okay?
你为什么这么抗拒这药啊
Why are you so resistant to the pill?
这是现代医学奇迹
It's a modern miracle!
这药改革了妇女们的命运
The pill revolutionized everything for women.
使我们女人能够出去工作
We were able to join the workforce.
-让我们...  -你这辈子都没工作过
- It allowed us to... - You never worked a day in your life.
但我想就可以去呀
But I could if I wanted to,
多亏这些「魔力」的药丸
thanks to this magic little pill.
那些药丸具有魔力吗
Those pills are magic?
来吧  本  我问你
Oh, here we go. Ben, let me ask you something.
如果有一种药能够让你
If there was a pill that gave you the freedom
随心所欲
to be anything in the whole world,
-你会吃吗  -必须滴
- would you take it? - Definitely.
瞧瞧  连三岁孩子都明白这个道理
There you go. This kid gets it and he's, like, three.
很好  那就给他吃吧
Great, then he can take 'em. How 'bout that?
行了  你回来
Okay, come back here.
别这样  塞布丽娜
Come on, Sabrina.
你关心我避不避孕干什么
What do you care what I do with my body?
你又不是我妈
You're not my mom.
亲爱的  就我而言
Honey, as far as I'm concerned,
只要我在这个家  我有两个任务
as long as I'm here, I have two jobs:
没人死  没人怀孕
make sure nobody dies or winds up pregnant.
没有死亡  没有出生
No deaths, no births.
你们这样合法吗
Is what you're doing even legal?
你才17岁
You're 17!
他有三十了吧
What is he, like 30?
其实康涅狄格州的法定年龄是16岁
Actually, the age of consent in Connecticut is 16.
什么
What?
康涅狄格州  跟一个16岁的女生上床是合法的
It's cool to have sex with a 16-year-old in the state of Connecticut.
我又没说这很棒
Well, not cool like "awesome."
就是允许而已
Cool like "acceptable."
恶心  你怎么知道的
Gross, how do you know that?
哥就是懂呗
I know what I know.
瓦哈卡州  12岁就可以了
12 in Oaxaca.
正视这个问题吧
Pull your head out of your ass!
这种错误能毁了你一生的
Come on, this is the kind of mistake that could ruin your life.
我不会怀孕的
I'm not gonna get pregnant.
幸亏本少爷不是女生
God, I'm so stoked I'm not a girl.
宝宝太烦人了
Babies freakin' suck.
这事男人也脱不了干系
Hey, it's a two-way street, pal.
亘古至今  女人就靠「意外怀孕」
Women have trapped men since the dawn of time
绑住男人的
by getting "accidentally" knocked up.
而你  绝对是头号目标
And you, my friend, are a prime target.
如果我是妞儿  我绝逼推到你
If I were a chick, I would take you down.
宝贝
Hey, babe.
吉米  你能跟我去卧室聊聊吗
Jimmy, can I have a word with you in the bedroom for a second?
为什么
Why?
当然可以了  好好好
Oh. Oh, yeah. Yeah, yeah, yep.
小伙伴们
Hey, guys.
凯  我能单独跟她聊聊吗
Kai, can you give us a little privacy, please?
-当然可以了  -谢谢
- Oh, yeah, absolutely. - Thanks.
-宝贝  还有需要吗  -没啦[很美]
- Babe, do you need anything? - I'm fine.
你确实美啊
Oh, yeah, you are.
好了  坐过去
Okay. Scooch over.
我坐过来了  不好意思
Here we go. Whoopsie daisy.
听着
So, listen,
我想了一下昨天我们的谈话
I was thinking about our conversation yesterday
我感觉自己有些老妈子上身了
and I feel like I came across kind of naggy.
我很抱歉
And I'm really sorry about that.
因为我懂  带套感觉不爽
Because I get it, condoms suck.
记得我上次谈这事时的反应吗
Remember how I felt about this conversation before?
我还是那个反应
Nothing's changed.
好吧  你先听我说完  好吗
All right, well, just hear me out, okay?
我去了免费诊所
I went down to the free clinic
因为免费  我替你好好「大捞了一把」
and I took full advantage of the "Free" Part for you.
发现  现在的年轻人选择太多了
Turns out, you kids have all sorts of options these days.
-什么  -天呐  简直了  瞧瞧
- What? - I mean, are you kidding me?Look at this.
比如这个  瞧瞧这小玩意
For instance, what's this little guy?
银色小袋子
Cute little silver package.
一个环
A ring!
就像个鱿鱼圈啊  不错
It's like a little piece of calamari. That's cool.
我不知道怎么用...
I don't know what you're supposed--
这要进...
does this go around the...
不不  要先挤压
Oh, no, no. Nope, you squish it,
然后捅进你的...
and you actually stick it up your...
然后...
and you are, uh--
就能覆雨翻云了
you're open for business.
是吗  很不错啊
Oh, yeah? Okay, cool, well,
跟避孕药中的雌激素成分一样
uh, it has the exact same hormones as the pill
还会造成血栓
and it causes blood clots.
别这么矫情行不行
Okay, try not to be a pain in the ass,
还有很多呢
we have a lot more here.
这个小玩意是什么
Now, what is this gizmo?
宫内避孕器
That's an IUD.
-听着就让人反胃  好长啊   -嗯
- Boy, it's off-putting. Very long. - Yeah.
但你知道上面写了什么吗
Oh, but you know what I see here?
无化学成分  无激素添加
No chemicals, no hormones.
-看来就是它啦  -不要
- Looks like we've got a winner! - Nope.
-张开腿  -别...
- Open wide. - Don't even...
「小飞机」要来啦
Yeah, here comes the airplane.
-别闹了  -我要捅进...
- Come on. - I'm gonna shove it all--
-我逗你呢  -我不要
- I'm just kidding. - I don't want it!
-我不会啦  你穿着裤子呢  -天呐
- I won't, you got pants on. - Oh, my God.
这东西的材质是铜
That thing is filled with copper.
来吧  你还想把什么「毒物」
Come on, do you have any other toxins
放进我身体呢
you want to fill me up with?
天呐  我这辈子没见过
Oh, my God, you are the dumbest smart person
你这么蠢的聪明人
I have ever met in my life.
好吧  你不想用避孕套
Fine, you don't want to use condoms,
我就只能当「避孕套」了
I guess I'll have to be the condom.
恶心死了  你什么意思
Gross, what does that even mean?
只要有我在
It means I will see to it
你和凯就别想无套做爱了
that you and Kai never have unprotected sex.
-怎么做  -我一没工作  二没爱好
- How? - I don't have a job or any hobbies;
我会想个招的
I'll figure something out.
米琪
Hey, Mickey.
你得签个字
I need your signature.
一向不爱签字
Yeah, I'm not big on paper trails.
这是干什么用的
What's it for?
我想了一下吉米的话
Well, I thought about what Jimmy said
我要去做结扎手术
and I'm gonna get a vasectomy.
结扎吗  你说什么呢
A vasectomy? What the hell are you talking about?
吉米说得对  我是被推到的主要目标
Jimmy's right, I got a big-ass target on my back.
吉米
Jimmy!
想想吧
Think about it:
我帅气多金又有才
I'm rich, i'm smart,
我就是「国民老公」啊
I look like a freakin' movie star,
性格又好
I'm kind,
还是个当爹的料
and I'd make a great dad.
外面那些网红锥子脸那么有心机
It's only a matter of time until some gold-digging whore
我迟早会着了她们的道
lures me into her honey trap.
怎么了
What's up?
奇普要去做结扎手术
Chip here is thinking about getting a vasectomy.
好极了  你想让我送他过去吗
Oh, right on. You want me to drive him or something?
不想  因为不能让他结扎
No, I don't, because he's not getting one.
我的身体
Hey, this is my body.
我的身体  我做主
I should be able to do whatever the hell I want with it!
-说得有道理  -行了  你就别多嘴了
- He's got a point. - Nah, don't you-- don't start.
不能让他去切蛋蛋  吉米
He's not getting his balls chopped off, Jimmy, okay?
不是切蛋蛋
Okay, that's not how it works.
其实只是个小手术
It's actually a pretty simple procedure.
夹住  剪开  封住
They clamp it, snip it, seal it.
我做过好几次了  结扎  解结扎...
I've had it done a couple times and reversed, so...
可他还没亲过女生呢
Okay, he hasn't even kissed a girl yet.
我亲过女生  亲过老多女生了
I've kissed girls, okay? I kiss-- I kiss mad girls!
行  证明一下吧
All right, prove it.
用你的手做示范  演示你怎么亲女生
Kiss your hand, show me how you kiss all these girls.
好
Okay...
别笑了  这不好笑
Stop laughing, it's not funny!
-抱歉  -怎么了啊
- I'm sorry. - What's going on?
没什么
Oh, nothing,
我就是拿奇普开涮
we're just, um, making fun of Chip
因为他没亲过女生
'cause he's never kissed a girl.
别着急  小家伙
don't sweat it, little man.
我三年级才亲上女生呢
I didn't have my first kiss till the third grade.
我13岁了
Well, I'm 13.
其实也没什么大不了
Well, there's nothing to it.
你只要闭上眼晴
All you got to do is just close your eyes,
让一切水到渠成
just let the wave wash over you.
不行  够了  好了
No, no, okay, all right, all right,
等下  停下  慢着
hold on. H-Hey. Hang on a second. Wait!
别亲了  别亲了
Just stop. Stop! Stop it!
给我打住
I mean... Stop!
出去  很好  很好
Get out. Good, good.
很好  真好啊
Good, really good.
身材不错  马一样健壮
Healthy. Healthy as a horse.
吉米  谈一下
Jimmy, a word.
什么
What?
天呐
Oh, my God.
你干什么啊
What are you doing?
不是吧
Oh, come on.
这样才对嘛
Yeah! There we go.
这里臭气熏天啊
Stinks in here.
该流通一下空气了
Get a little air flow going.
你脑子有病啊
What are you, insane?
除了盯着我  你就没事干了吗
You have nothing better to do than to stalk me?
避孕套
你们出个声同意就行了
You guys just say the word.
给我吧  我们会试的  你个蛇精病
Just give 'em to me, we'll try 'em, you maniac.
这才像话嘛
Now we're talking.
你们爽翻吧
You kids go nuts.
怎么了啊  小少爷
What is the problem, slugger?
我们学校的女生都是可怕的女汉子
All the girls at my school are stupid trolls!
你来找我就对了
Oh, well, you were smart to come to me.
我没找你  你跑到我屋里来了
I didn't, you walked into my room.
不要在意细节
Yeah, either way.
说说这些女汉子吧  小子
Tell me about these trolls, pal.
她们...
They're--
她们不可怕  就是...
they're not trolls, okay, they just...
她们...
they won't...
如果我告诉你
Okay, if I tell you,
你得保证守口如瓶
you have to promise not to tell anybody.
当然了
Yeah, of course.
米琪没说错  我没亲过女生
Mickey's right, I never... kissed a girl, ever.
我学了凯的路数
I tried to do it like Kai,
但结果不是人见人爱  而是人见人踹
but they all treated me like I had freakin' AIDS.
好吧  那确实很无知  很不近人情
Okay, that's ignorant and insensitive,
我懂被人拒绝的滋味
but I get how it feels to be rejected.
信我
Trust me, uh...
而至于凯
All right, and Kai,
他帅到没朋友...
he's so good looking, it's--
我要是女人  都想找他来一发
I wouldn't mind taking a run at him myself.
而且因为他的存在
And he is really giving your aunt and I
你小姨和我才有性福可享
a jump-start in the bedroom.
恶心  老兄  少儿不宜啊
Oh, gross, dude. Know your audience.
抱歉  我只是想说
I'm sorry. Look, all I'm saying is
你得做自己  懂吗
you got to be yourself, okay.
别想着凯和他的颜值了
Forget Kai and his looks.
你拥有的东西  他未必有
You've got things that he doesn't have, right?
你得发挥你的长处
You got to play to those, play to your strengths.
对  发挥我的优势
Right, play to my strengths.
-谢谢  吉米  -没事
- Thank you, Jimmy. - Yeah.
楼上搞什么呀
What the heck is going on up there?
你姐正被搞...  正搞一些家具呢
Your sister's getting fu... rniture... delivered.
画得不错
Pretty cool drawing.
不是  画得太差了
No, it's not. It's terrible.
你这么成天盯着我
And how am I supposed to make anything good
我怎么画好啊
when you won't stop breathing down my neck?!
小本本  你咋啦
Whoa, Benny, what is going on with you, bud?
最近这么暴躁
You're so moody these days.
米琪小姐  这是我在塞布丽娜的垃圾桶里看到的
Ms. Mickey? Look, I found these in Sabrina's trash.
不是吧
Are you serious?
你得答应我  你不会让她被搞大肚子
You have to promise me you will not let her get pregnant, okay--
你发誓
prometame.
我发誓
I prometa. Okay?
我已经养大了塞布丽娜  奇普和本
I already raised Sabrina, Chip, and Ben.
再多一个宝宝  我会崩坏的  成天哭闹
I cannot do another, not with all the crying and the--
- 整夜不睡觉  还得换尿片  -我懂  好了
- and the no sleeping and the diapers. - I get it. Hey, hey, yes...
-屎尿成灾啊  -我明白了  好了
- There are just so many diapers. - I understand, okay.
不不不  你不懂
No, no, no, you don't understand.
我母乳喂养了那三个孩子
I breastfed all three of them.
我的奶子已经变成咬成口香糖了
My nipples are like old chewing gum.
我不听我不听  你够啦
No, no, no, but come on, good God, that's enough.
我会想个招的
I'll figure it out, okay.
就再跟我提你奶子的事了
I don't want to hear about your nipples anymore.
-行吗  -没问题  没问题
- Are we cool on that? - Yeah, we're good. We're good.
-这就好  -但我们得棒打鸳鸯了
- Okay, good. - But we got to keep her from seeing him.
这招只会有反效果
No, that's the classic thing.
越是阻止她们交往
If we forbid her to see him,
她就会越想跟他在一起
she's just going to want him more.
我们得让她甩了他
We got to make her break up with him.
怎么了
What?
老娘要上了那个小鲜肉
I'm going to bang his beautiful brains out.
-够狠  -没错
- Oh... yeah. - Oh... yeah.
米琪  我感觉这不太好
Mickey, I got a bad feeling about this.
塞布丽娜知道你上了她男友
Sabrina is going to do the murder to you
她会杀了你
if you sleep with Kai.
没事  她很快就不会计较了
Yeah, well, she'll get over it.
我觉得这么损的招  该由我来出手
I think it should be me who carries out this despicable act.
艾尔巴  你肯献身真大度啊
Oh, Alba, that is very generous of you,
但不用了
but not necessary.
你已经为这个家做得太多了
You already do so much for this family.
其实也没做多少
Oh, well, I really don't do a lot,
我最近一直偷懒
and I've been slacking off.
没事  我来出马吧
Yeah, it's okay. I-- I do this.
你太贴心了  但是呢
Yeah, super thoughtful, but you know what?
问题是这样
Here's the thing.
凯都「久经情场」了
Kai's a thoroughbred, right,
还是派我这种经验丰富的「骑师」搞定吧
and we really need an experienced jockey riding that horse.
但如果我能...
Yeah, but if I could just take a...
别跟老娘抢男人  艾尔巴  我来出马
Back off, Alba, okay? I'm doing my plan.
有人吗  女士
Hello? Ma'am?
能让你听个动静就知足吧
Just be grateful you get to listen.
-有人吗  -你好啊
-Hello? - Oh, hey, you.
我收到你的短信了
I got your message.
你的床出问题了吗
There's something wrong with your bed?
直接切入正题啊
Jumping right into it, huh?
姐喜欢  想喝杯酒吗
I like that. Want to have a drink first?
不用了  不喝
Oh, no, I'm okay.
我要干活  不能喝酒
You know, booze and power tools.
好吧  我替你喝了
All right, I'll take yours.
这床出什么问题了
So, um, what seems to be the problem over here?
「她」就像裤门大开「叫个不停」呢
Oh, man, she's creaking like a barn door.
-是吗  -没错
- Oh, yeah? - Yep.
我应该能拧紧一些螺丝
Well, I guess I could tighten a few screws,
但我看着挺好呢
but it looks good to me.
我看着也挺好呢
It looks good to me, too.
好吧  我来看看
Yeah, okay. Um, let's see.
还是没听到任何声响
Yeah, you know, I'm still not really hearing anything.
你没听到吗  好吧
You're not hearing it? Yeah.
我知道问题出在哪儿了
Oh, I think I know what the problem is.
一般我会跳上床「上位」
Normally I'm, huh, on top of it
才会听到叫声  懂我意思吗
when I'm hearing the noises, you know what I mean?
就像...
It's, kind of, like...
这样一直叫个不停呢
squeak... squeak... squeak, squeak.
你听到了吗
You hearing it at all?
没有  没听到
Yeah, you know, I'm not hearing it.
好吧  那我们重新再来一次吧
Oh, okay. Well, then I guess let's just start over.
我们不用去多想
We don't have to overthink it.
-我们到床下  解决...  -不要
- Let's go under the bed and we'll figure out sort of a... - N-No.
我就是想离开这里
I just want to get out of this here.
我还是...  败给你了
You know what, maybe I should-- okay.
-等下  等下  -好吧
- Well, hold on. Hang on a second. - Okay.
如果你给我几秒钟  我们就能...
I think if we-- you just gave me a second, we could--
摔得我心慌慌啊
My goodness, what a launch.
你要走了吗  走吧  滚出我房间
Are you-- are you leaving? Leave. Get out of here.
滚出我房间
Get out of my room.
滚出去  别再回来了
Get out of my room and do not come back.
我要是出马  就拿下了
I could've closed the deal.
人艰不拆  艾尔巴  人艰不拆
Not now, Alba, okay? Not now.
那个小贱人  她想怀孕  行行
Oh, that bitch, if she wants to get pregnant, fine, fine.
我们就让她怀孕
We're going to help her get pregnant.
小黛
Hey, Steffi.
奇普
Hey, Chip.
你参加那个数学考试了吗
So, uh, did you take that math test?
天呐  太难了
Oh, my God, it was so hard.
就是啊  这是代数
Right? It's like, are we in algebra or,
还是空间研究计划啊
like, the freakin' space program?
「地球呼叫代数  没人待见你」
Like, "Earth to algebra, nobody likes you."
不错吧  好玩吧
So cool, cool... chill.
我就是觉得
Well, I just, like, think you're really,
你特别漂亮  人也特别好
really pretty and, like, super cool,
我很喜欢跟你在一起
and I like hanging out with you and stuff.
你这人很好相处
And, like, you're super freakin' chill
跟你处得很开心
and, like, all that good stuff.
奇普  不用这么紧张
Chip, you don't have to be so nervous.
直接问我吧
You can just ask.
好
Okay.
我就是想知道...
Well, I was just wondering if I--
-我能给你五百块让你跟我亲热吗  -什么
- I could pay you $500 to make out with me? - What?
你值更多  一千块
Um, you're better than that. $1,000.
你个混蛋
You jerk.
天呐  艾尔巴  你在那杯奶昔里放了多少催吐剂啊
Damn, Alba, how much ipecac did you put in that smoothie?
我就是想造成害喜的假象
I'm just trying to fake morning sickness,
不是让她吐死
not blow her guts out.
我又不是你  总给人下药
I'm sorry I'm not the expert drugger like you.
确实不是  所以你们幸好有我
No, you're not. You guys are lucky to have me here.
瞧我在网上买到什么了  假的验孕棒
Look what I got online, a bunch of fake pregnancy tests.
我换掉了普多洗手台下面的真验孕棒
I replaced them with all the ones under Poodle's sink.
一般把验孕棒给男人看
You hand a guy something like this,
他就直接甩你钱去处理掉
he just starts throwing cash at you, no questions asked.
我称之为「六百块脱胎换骨」
I like to call it the $600 shuffle.
我听完之后  内心无比压抑
Yeah, now I just feel depressed.
你们俩捣鼓什么呢
What are you two doing?
没什么呀  我们就是
Oh, us? Nothing. We're-- we're just,
-就是随便聊聊  -嗯
- you know, we're hanging out. - Yeah.
不是  你俩表现很诡异
No, you're acting weird.
我们没有
No, we are not.
我们俩可正常了
We are acting as regular as can be.
嗯
Yeah.
你们就是  我知道原因
Yes, you are, and I know why.
你们不敢明说讨厌我的画
You don't want to tell me that you hate my drawing.
你觉得我我没有画画的天赋
You think I don't have control of the marker,
我搞艺术就是浪费生命
and this whole art thing is a waste of my time.
不用你们说了  我已经造啦
Well, you don't have to tell me because I already know.
真是个熊孩子
What a dick.
那小家伙怎么了
What's wrong with him?
不知道  你怎么了
I don't know. What's wrong with you?
-你看起来不太好啊  -是啊
- You look horrible. - Oh, yeah.
我病了一天了  不知道怎么了
Well, I've been sick all day. I don't know.
以后上学期间不能再喝酒了
I think I got to stop drinking on school nights, you know?
-也许你肚子里有了宝宝呢  -好了
- Or maybe you have a baby inside you. - Oh, okay.
那不可能  她一直都用避孕套了吧
Well, that's not possible 'cause she's using condoms, right?
-没错  当然了  -我就是随口一说
- Right. Yeah, of course. - Yeah, I'm just saying,
不如你去普多卫生间找个验孕棒
maybe you want to take one of the pregnancy tests
验一下吧  保险起见嘛
in Poodle's bathroom, you know, just to be sure.
她说得有道理  验下又无妨
She's got a good point. It couldn't hurt.
但我不...
Well, I-- I mean, I don't...
天呐  快去吐吧
Oh, no. Get it out.
不是吧
Oh, no, no.
她那么瘦
She's a tiny person.
一小滴就行了  懂吗
Just a little drip, you know what I mean?
小子  很高兴你打来找了我
Hey, buddy, I'm glad you called.
-我找的是米琪  -我来了
- I called Mickey. - Yeah, well, I'm here.
-有什么问题  -你就是问题
- What's the problem? - You're the problem.
我照你说的做了  发挥我的优势
I-I did what you said. I played to my strengths,
结果小黛把我的蛋蛋踢碎了
and Steffi booted my nuts into my throat.
没事  别担心  会康复的
Yeah. Well, don't worry, they'll drop back down.
-我讨厌女生  -别这样
- I freakin' hate girls. - Hey, come on.
你还这么年轻  生活才刚刚开始
You're a young man. This is just beginning.
说句实话吧
All right? And to tell you the truth,
我怀念以前女生爆我蛋蛋来着
I miss the days girls were blasting me in the junk.
你是他父亲吗
Are you the father?
今天算是
I am today.
他的扫描结果没什么问题
Well, his scans look okay.
希望疼肿几天后会慢慢消退
Hopefully the pain and swelling will subside in the next few days,
但如果没有
but if not,
可能表示问题比较严重  甚至可能不育
that could mean something more serious, maybe even infertility.
这是什么意思
What does-- what does that mean?
他...
Well, his...
这表示你如愿以偿了
I think it means you got your wish.
恭喜你第一次「结扎」
Congrats on your first vasectomy.
我越想就越觉得
And the more that I think about it,
生不了孩子也没什么
it's not the worst thing I can't have kids--
我可以领养啊
I can always adopt.
谁被你领养真是倒八辈子血霉了
I would not wish that on any abandoned child in the world.
米琪  她来了
Mickey. She's coming.
-是吗  -她来了  来了
- Yeah? - She's coming, she's coming.
好了好了  别太激动  装一下
Okay, okay. Shh. Keep a straight face, okay.
淡定一些
All right, play it cool.
我们要让她被自己蠢哭
We're going to make her look like a real scumbag.
-她肯定会崩坏的  -没错
- She is going to freak. - Yeah.
各位
Hi, everybody.
我和凯有消息宣布
Uh, so, Kai and I, we have some news.
什么消息  我怎么可能会知道呢
What? What is this news? I don't know what it could be.
好了  什么消息啊
Okay, what is the news?
我不知道怎么开口  我就...
I don't really know how to say this, so I'm just gonna...
-就直接说了  -说吧
- put it out there. - Go for it.
我怀孕了
I'm pregnant.
这下好了  佩莫顿的第一条分支血脉
There we go. The first dilution of the Pemberton bloodline.
我太惊讶了
Well, this is shocking.
我之前完全不知情
I had zero ideas about this.
谁知道这是真的啊  真丢脸啊
Who would ever know this to be true? Shame, shame.
如你所见  我们很惊讶
As you can see, we are shocked, okay,
你就是个白痴  塞布丽娜
and you are a moron, Sabrina.
你怎么能这样呢
How could you do this?
我就跟你说会这样了
I told you this was going to happen.
你说得对  我就是个大白痴
You were right. I'm a big stupid idiot.
我的人生就此完了
My whole life is ruined.
你对「我家」闺女做了什么  你个畜...
What did you do to our little girl, you son of...?
别别别  别动手  住手
No, no, no, no, no, no. Stop it. No, no, no.
抱歉  两位  抱歉
It's a-- sorry. You guys, I'm sorry.
这是个误会
This is a big misunderstanding.
这位大姐  恕我直言  我来哄她
Ma'am, ma'am, with all due respect, I got this.
宝贝  看着我  我爱你
Babe, babe, look at me, okay. Listen to me, I love you.
我们就要有宝宝了
And we're going to have a baby.
-这就是问题了  -这位大姐
- Yeah, well, that's the thing. - Ma'am!
这多棒啊
How cool is that?
我可以给宝宝造张床  造个小木马
I get to build him a crib and a rocking horse,
还要建个小房子放这些
and a whole friggin' house to put it all in.
我是说
I mean...
这么说吧
you know what?
豁出去了
Screw it.
-这是什么剧本啊  -这位大姐
- What the hell is happening? - Ma'am!
塞布丽娜·佩莫顿
Sabrina Pemberton,
我爱你
I love you.
你愿意嫁给我吗  宝贝
Will you marry me, baby?
我愿意
Yes, I will marry you.
好吧  我刚才要说的问题就是
Okay, great. Yeah, that's the thing I was going to say
她没怀孕
is that she's not pregnant.
-没事了  -什么
- That's good. - What?
她没怀孕  你没怀孕
She's not pregnant. You're not pregnant.
-什么意思  -我和艾尔巴...
- What do you mean? - Alba and I--
我们想让你吸取教训  所以我们...
well, we wanted to teach you a lesson, you know, so we...
希望你吸取教训了
So I-I hope you learned.
演不下去了  脱离剧本了
I can't-- it's gone off the rails a bit.
我不知道怎么演下去
I'm not really sure...
好吧  谢谢你
Okay. Well, thank you.
不客气
Yes, you're welcome.
谢什么啊
Wait, for what?
如果你没这么做
Well, if you didn't do that,
我就不会知道凯是个负责任的好男人
I never would've found out what an amazing man Kai is.
天呐  你还是想娶我吗
Oh, my God, do you still want to marry me?
-啥  -非常想
- What? - More than anything.
没怀孕  假怀孕
No. No baby, fake baby.
你说的都是一个意思
Yeah, that's the same thing, though.
听到了吗  都是一个意思
You hear that? It's kind of the same thing.
塞布丽娜要结婚了
Sabrina's getting married
等下
Wait...
塞布丽娜要结婚了
Sabrina's getting married?
这小家伙到底是怎么了
Okay, what the hell's going on with this one?
我又开心  又难过
I'm happy and sad...
还很生气
and mad.
小本本  你究竟是咋啦
Come on, Ben, what's going on with you, buddy?
我就是个没艺术细胞的小废柴
I'm just a big, fat, no-talent loser.
即使你的「魔力药丸」都拯救不了我
Even your magic pills couldn't help.
-什么「魔力药丸」  -你包里的那些啊
- What magic pills? - The ones in your purse.
我换成了其他药
I filled with other pills
这样就不会被抓包
so I wouldn't get in trouble.
你是说我的避孕药吗
You are talking about my birth control?
这可不妙  因为我和吉米最近经常「运动」
That's not good, 'cos Jimmy and I have been... a lot.
-我要当爹啦  -不不不
- I am gonna be a dad. - No, no, no.
我要当爹啦
I am gonna be a dad.
字幕组
ZiMuZu.tv
原创翻译  双语字幕
最快首发美剧日剧下载请登录
字幕组网站www.ZiMuZu.tv
翻译:  兔牙Bobby猫
校对:  兔牙Bobby猫
时间轴:  壬虚浪影
后期:  鱼骨头
总监： 兔牙Bobby猫